# VICTOR WILLIAMS

Full Stack Developer

444 N 4<sup>th</sup> Street, 401 Philadelphia, PA 19123

484-895-5489

vrwilliams719@gmail.com

# **OBJECTIVE**

Freelance software developer with strong analytical skills and proficiency in mathematics. Individual with ability to follow established procedures and work under little or no supervision. Bringing expertise in writing full-stack code to support multiple platforms, including web, android, and iOS, and a solid grasp of data structures and object- oriented designs.

# EDUCATION -

# **Temple University**,

Philadelphia, PA May 2019

- Bachelor of Arts: Criminal Justice and Information Science and Technology Certificate: Computer Security
- •Studied the subjects of Discrete Mathematics, Differential Calculus, Data Structures, Algorithms, and Operating Systems within the Computer Science Curriculum.

# EXPERIENCE

#### **AmeriCorps**

Aug. 2019 - Jan. 2020

Information Technology Manager

- •Refined and improved the existing documentation within the system
- •Web development and maintenance for various School District websites
- •Manage and repair all technology in Taggart John H. School

# BitGamer

Nov. 2018 - Nov. 2019

Full Stack Developer / Tournament Organizer

- •Developed a tournament hosting web application along with a small team
- •Communicated with other companies to increase collaborative business opportunities
- •Manage the social media platforms for the company's likeness

# CrystalFruit

Dec. 2016 – July 2018

Full Stack Developer

- •Developed full-stack web applications which processed, analyzed, and rendered data
- •Maintain and update websites upon request per client
- •Planned, wrote, and debugged web applications and software with complete accuracy

# KEY SKILLS -

Node.JS, Android, Rust, HTML5, Java, MongoDB, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Go, Python, AngularJS, CSS, C#, SQL, and Swift

#### ACTIVITIES

Temple University Development Team EBoard, Volunteer CS Tutor, Temple University (ACM) Association for Computing Machinery PennApps at University of Pennsylvania Alliance for Minority Participation in STEM The Odyssey Online The Tab Let's Get Ready SAT Prep Program Owlchestra, Violinist